

## **ABOUT ME**

I'm a game programmer specializing in **object-oriented programming**, with 2 years and a half of experience in the industry.

I have worked at Melbot, where I was involved in game development and **publishing for consoles**, as well as handling their ports.

Additionally, I have gained experience working for Magnetic, where I focused on mobile game development for a live game.

Furthermore, I successfully launched my own Android game and completed several internships.

I'm a very enterprising person, outgoing and eager for new experiences.

# CONTACT

- +34 636-98-24-40
- Portfolio Personal web
- LinkedIn

## **LANGUAGES**

- Spanish (Native)
- Catalan (Native)
- English (Advanced)

# **MARINA CHAVARRIA**

**GAME PROGRAMMER** 

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Console Game Programmer - Melbot

January 2022-April 2023 October 2023 - Current

## Nick Jr Party Adventure - PC & Console

- Implement key gameplay systems. (level, menus, rewards...)
  - Re-develop a new UI system with DoTween, for improved performance.
- Develop the PlayStation 5 port and supported the PlayStation 4 port.
- Optimizing the game for Switch due to its limitations.
- Developed a tool for creating levels that was highly flexible, allowing designers and artists to seamlessly incorporate their artwork into the tool, with the map adapting to the art.

## My Little Pony - PC & Console

- Develop gameplay features.
- Responsible for the port Play Station 5 port.
- Enhance its performance and resolve existing bugs.
- Working with the Nintendo SDK and Xbox to assist in the development.

# Mobile Game Programmer - Magnetic

April 2023 - October 2023

#### Art Heist Puzzle - Android and IOS

- Developed significant features for a live game.
- Implementation of code for the client-server communication.
- · Actively applied dependency injection in the codebase.
- Integrated third-party libraries into existing projects to extend functionality.
- Debugged complex problems in existing code base.
- Develop the first in-game purchase system for the game, from the client side.
- Participated in design meetings with other team members to discuss ideas for future content.

## **EDUCATION**

## **Videogame Programming and Design**

2018 - 2023

Tecnocampus Pompeu Fabra

#### COMPETENCES

#### Languages

- C#
- C++
- Lua
- Python

#### **Engines**

- Unity
- Unreal
- Defold

# SOFT SKILLS

- Communication
- · Problem-Solving
- Teamwork
- · Attention to detail
- Time managment